I
Think
Hey everybody welcome back I'm clearly in a good mood because I'm going thrifting Yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
I've done this video two other times and they're actually like one of my favorite
videos to film I love taking you guys thrifting.
I just love going thrifting and I always feel like it's so fun to do
it with friends Obviously in this video, I'm gonna be doing it alone, but you
guys are my friends So I'm taking you guys along with me and we're gonna
thrift my dream winter wardrobe in my other two thrift with me videos I was
back home in Chicago where the thrift stores are a little bit more limited as
opposed to New York City Which is so dense in thrift stores and vintage clothing
stores The only thing is the price point is a lot higher So the goal
of today's video is to still keep it original type of thrifting not how it
is now where everything's like super super Expensive I wrote down a list of stores
around Manhattan that are mostly secondhand stores.
They're not like curated vintage stores today We're gonna go to lower Manhattan.
We're gonna be around Parsons and NYU my idea is that all the stylish kids
go there So whatever clothes they don't want they put in the you know in
the Goodwills and the crossroads like all those things So I don't know.
We'll see if I'm smart for that Anyways, I have a wish list.
My first tip for thrifting is that it's very smart to go in with a
clear vision in mind Maybe make a mood board on Pinterest or screenshot a bunch
of like outfit inspo you see on Instagram on TikTok I have a theme for
this thrift trip.
It's 90s minimal slash supermodel chic, which is very like simple clothing yet It's sexy
silhouettes.
It's flowy.
It's somehow still form-fitting and the color palette that I'm gonna be thrifting today That's
also my second tip.
Thrift with a color palette in mind.
Otherwise, you're just gonna buy a bunch of random stuff I really want to find
clothing that is olive colored, chocolate browns, charcoal gray, light gray, black and white, cream,
just simple, sleek clothing that I can definitely layer on top of and use all
together.
Because it's wintertime.
That's what winter is for, is to layer and to use a bunch of pieces
and have fun with it.
So let's go.
I'm really excited.
Our first store is going to be Crossroads.
See you there.
Watching that back, I realized I actually did not give you guys my wish list,
just the general theme.
Let me quickly run it down for you so you're not confused.
I'm looking for a black cardigan, maybe an olive sweater or cardigan.
I need a lot of sweaters So that's the main goal is just sweater sweater
sweater a chunky bangle or ring.
That's like the enamel material I don't know if I'm saying that correctly maybe wooden
bangles things of cool materials and different colors I want really cool button-ups or blouses
Maybe striped polka dot and then of course for it to be within my color
palette and then we'll see what else we find The world is my oyster.
It's our oyster.
Now we can actually go
upon entrance the first thing that caught my eye was the massive wall of bags
i actually never seen such a big selection at a thrift store i feel like
at least in my past experience one of the first things that caught my eye
was this bright red truligin little bag i liked it but i didn't love how
modern in a way it looks i really tend to look for more vintage style
bags so i ended up leaving it behind and then i just racked through for
a little bit longer lots of like satchels i know.
Kind of cool, but nothing, nothing interesting.
I've been secretly wanting a beret for so long.
I feel like it'd be so chic for the fall and winter season to spice
up any outfit, but I'm not gonna lie, I don't love how they look on
me as much as I wish I did.
And then we got into the nitty-gritty of it all.
I was obsessed with this crossroads.
The selection was insane.
I'm almost 100% sure it was because it was next to a fashion school.
When I got to trying on, there was quite a few like good name brands
for reasonable prices.
I found a lot of sweaters mostly because i stuck to the sweater and long
sleeve section i really like this anina bing sweater this was a cute little i
don't even know how to describe this looking back i actually love how the sleeves
bubble up at the shoulders knowing myself i would have loved it in the moment
and then probably would never actually grab it from my closet whenever it's not a
complete definite yes i just decide to leave it behind
okay this um i'm still in shock i found this and that it was in
plain sight and it wasn't snatched up quicker than you would expect i was so
lucky to have found it maybe somebody had just put it out or something because
not only is this a Guess Faux Fur Coat, the color is insane.
It was $20.
Like I am spoiling a little bit.
I'm foreshadowing the thrift haul.
Of course I got this.
Are you kidding?
Look at it.
It's insane.
So I was super excited I found this.
Okay and this was another amazing find.
This is a Marc Jacobs cable knit sweater.
The most luxurious thick sweater I've ever put on my body.
Everything was incredible until I find holes.
holes in the sleeves this was the most upsetting thing like i was so obsessed
with this i just i couldn't bear the disappointment but i had to leave it
behind because there was no fixing it up next is thrift nyc this was like
right around the corner from crossroads i was overstimulated to say the least i personally
love to put in my headphones listen to my own music and kind of be
in my own world when i'm thrifting so anytime i go into a thrift store
and it is the most obnoxiously loud music blasting throughout the store.
I can't.
I can't do it.
There's already so many things to like take in but yeah I kind of left
quickly because I needed a break.
Shortly after was Beacon's Closet.
I'm pretty sure I've been to this exact location like two years ago.
It was insane.
Like great items.
Price is not so great though I will say a lot of options, a lot
of shoes.
If you're looking for designer items that are more fairly priced as opposed to like
a curated designer store i would go here but that was not what i was
looking for by the end though i think everybody had just gone out of school
so like half of parsons was inside this beacon's closet it was mayhem
all
right it's the next day which means we're going thrifting again Hence the title of
the video.
Today we're going to a few different thrift shops in the Chelsea area.
If you guys didn't know, I currently go to Fashion Institute of Technology, which is
a fashion college in Chelsea, Manhattan.
There's actually quite a few thrift stores right around the area.
There's like a Goodwill, a Salvation Army, but the two that we're going to start
off at is Buffalo Exchange and Second Street.
Those are a little bit more curated.
I've actually been to that Buffalo Exchange when I first visited FIT, and I found
the most insane pair of Chloe wedge heels for only $40.
They have a really good selection.
I'm really excited.
and we're right by my school, which is great.
If I need to use the bathroom, I can literally just like go to my
school.
I don't know.
I don't know why that came to mind.
Looking for the same things, although I think today I am gonna have more of
an eye out for accessories and shoes.
Yesterday, I was solely looking at tops, which I still will do.
You can never have too many tops.
Bottoms, you can always like rotate.
Tops, the more the merrier, in my opinion.
Another big thrifting tip that I have is always dress comfortably and wear something that
you can easily slip on and off, as well as wear something basic because in
the occasion that the thrift store does not have a fitting room.
It's nice to wear just a simple tank top.
I'm wearing just jeans.
And then you can try things on easily and see how it would look.
I'm wearing Uggs so I have ultimate walking comfort.
Dress comfortably.
All right let's go.
Okay I love second street shops.
I've been to a few.
I've been to one back home in Chicago.
I've been to one in Japan and this was the second one I've been to
in New York City.
I love how everything is so organized.
They have labels for every single section whether it's just broken down by like blouses
sweaters pants they also have like y2k they have grunge they have street wear i
had a really good time in the second street just rocking through the shoes were
great i spent quite a good amount of time looking at their shoes i love
this pair of brown heels downside is i didn't see a fitting room i'm pretty
sure there isn't one in the second street then i walked by this random store
it was literally right by second street it's called garage sale vintage um it's also
a bar it It was such a cool store.
Definitely more like vintage, old-esque style clothing.
Again, headed to the sweaters.
I really liked this BCBG sweater.
I just, the low V, I don't really know.
I guess I tanked up under, but too casual for what I was aiming for.
A lot of nice colors, purples, blues.
Then I found this little gray button-up cardigan.
I really like the pearl buttons on it.
all
right
i think it's time for a haul so you guys came thrifting with me yesterday
and the day before that i was debating going thrifting again today but i figured
it would be smartest to just stop here my previous thrift hauls have been quite
big and that's because they're from my local Goodwill where I can just buy like
a top for five dollars.
It's very different here in New York so but I'm very very happy with what
I got.
Also I don't have that much space in my apartment so I have to be
extra picky about the clothes I do allow into my space.
I think I was very intentional this time around.
I've become such a picky shopper which I really appreciate about myself because I used
to be a shopping addict.
Yeah not anymore thank god.
Anyways here are some receipts and here is the goodies.
The goodies.
I think we should start off with our first location which was indeed Crossroads.
That was my favorite thrift store.
I will be returning.
If I would have gotten thrifting today, I would have gone back to that one.
Or the Crossroads in East Village, which is also really good.
So if you ever come to New York or you live in New York and
you want to go thrifting, I would suggest Crossroads.
It has a place in my heart.
I can't- and you can sell your clothes there too, which is great.
So let's start off with a bang, shall we?
Oh my god.
Guess, guess, guess mama.
I love guess.
Faux fur coat.
Do you see the color of this?
I'm just now thinking and realizing it's kind of giving Corolla de Veau, which I
love.
I've always wanted to dress up as her for Halloween.
I've yet to do so but anyways, I think it is stunning It is not
the warmest thing the interior inner lining is like very flimsy.
I guess you could say it's very thin The sleeves don't keep me warm at
all and I tested this theory because on Friday night I went out and I
wore this you guys I went to a restaurant.
I walk in within five seconds I sit down the two ladies next to me
plus the person I was with Complimented my coat and they were like, oh my
god, that is stunning.
That is beautiful all these things.
I was like, thank you Thank you.
Thank you.
Yes, I know.
I was biting my tongue not to tell them that I literally had thrifted it
earlier that day I'm so proud of it.
So I'm like glowing right now.
Like I'm just like beaming with joy.
I love it Like it was made for me.
It's meant for me.
And it buttons up which is really really nice The buttons are super discreet.
I barely noticed them which is nice cuz it'll keep me warm-er than if it
were just like open facing This is like the first actual full fur piece that
I have.
I have one other coat that's like fur lined.
This?
Ooh, we're off to a great start if you ask me.
Okay, sorry, that was the longest I'll probably talk about an item.
Next!
Okay, I was really excited about this.
I love to have nice lounge wear to kind of prance around in my apartment
at home.
And something that keeps me warm, because my apartment is not the warmest.
I don't know, this heater, she's picky with when she wants to disperse heat.
So I was really excited when I found this beautiful little slouchy cardigan, black and
gray striped.
I told you guys I was kind of looking for stripes, polka dots.
I love those type of patterns in my clothing.
This is actually an All Saints cardigan.
I got this for $29.87.
So that was Friday.
I did end up going to two or three more stores after that.
Didn't find anything there.
Yesterday, I started off at 2nd Street.
I have a larger shoe size, so thrifting shoes in the first place can be
quite difficult.
Vintage shoes, older shoes, or just like a common shoe size I always see is
like a 7 or an 8 in women's.
Perfect, beautiful, Pristine Coach Pumps.
I have another pair of Coach Pumps, not Coach Pumps, mules that I got on
thredUP and to this day they're my prized possession and these are just, they're brand
new and also I love that the inner, what is this, like the sole?
It's like a little metallic detailing.
I love the studs.
I love the chocolate brown color.
I told you guys I was looking for chocolate brown clothing or accessories, whatever it
may be.
I'm obsessed.
I also don't own very many pumps.
Most of my heels are actually like an open back.
So this will be nice, especially for the wintertime because if I do want to
dress it up I can have that extra support.
A girl can never have too many heels.
They're super comfortable, which is always really nice when you have a heel.
So I'm just really excited about how incredible of a condition they're in.
I saw them on the shelf, snatched them right up, and I was like, oh,
beautiful.
That was Second Street.
Very happy with that.
And then I popped into this random store that I had no idea about, but
it was right next to Second Street.
I've been wanting black leather gloves in general for the wintertime, especially, I don't know
why, in my head I've always imagined this little detailing here.
On top of that, a little extra layer I've been looking for fur lined black
leather gloves.
So when I saw these it was like right before I was about to leave
I was like wait a second Let me try them on.
A little small like they're a little bit of a hassle to get on but
they fit nonetheless And I think they're beautiful.
This is the try on for this item.
I love this little like buckle detailing over here super chic Keep my fingers nice
and warm this winter.
Last place was Buffalo Exchange.
I was really struggling in there I'm not gonna lie.
I was feeling kind of overstimulated, tired I guess my final tip is always go
in with something in your stomach energy and be in the mood for it Otherwise,
you're not gonna last drifting can take it out of you.
So if you're not there with a good headspace Good luck, babe.
But nonetheless, I did end up finding this beautiful Missoni missoni mama v-neck buttoned up
slouchy long-sleeve cardigan you could say I love it.
I love the detailing I love this texture that's on the cardigan.
It's a very nice material It's almost like a little sheer see-through moment.
Super super cute Not a huge fan of this like little orange pink line stripe
thing going around but it's not super noticeable.
I would say overall I love it.
I also love how there's kind of like a ruffly sleeve going on I'm very
excited to stop this as like nice little piece.
This was $30 So that is what I found thrifting in New York If you guys
want to see more videos like this if you enjoyed watching this video I have
so many other places around the city that I've either been to and would love
to go to again or or haven't been to and would love to go thrift
at.
So if you guys are interested, let me know and I can definitely make more,
more of these videos.
And you know I love to thrift.
The seasons are always changing.
My style is ever evolving.
So I hope you guys enjoyed watching me thrift again.
If you've never seen the thrift with me I did back home in the summertime,
I'll link it.
You guys should go watch it because it was pretty fun and I found a
lot of things then.
I love you so much.
I will see you in next week's video.
Mwah, mwah, mwah.
Love ya.
you